review proposals select proposal
get contracts go no go bye
here link in the description below
insurance consider subscribing and
hitting that notification bell
follows the facebook page at business
reviews vlog
[Music]
number
for that one flight for that boat ride
that luggage
dengue is a word to define constant
guinea gamete insurance partisan
out-of-pocket expenses big among
diagnostics
er consultation laboratory tests hmo is
a term
type of policy pakistan
number one amount of time covered car no
insurance policy
coverage term example prepaid policy
hmo participants in cover by a
particular amount oh
yeah by a particular span of time up to
age
ganito termination of coverage
policy now term non-policy term can also
mean a policy type prepaid
hmo or traditional a traditional type of
insurance policy
can be regular or a term type of policy
number four we need the term to refer to
payment terms
10 year term so 10 years come on by
every year
or for 20 years annually quarterly for
10 years
every five years number two at a
particular
so usually 65 or 75 it's a renewable
term
diagnosis
profitable
instead of paying for something like
that i'd rather be liquid whole life
is a type of insurance critical illness
at a particular age
i'd rather not put a future commitment
for something in the offshore buying
what you can afford
realistically wool vol is a more complex
product i don't like wool
the reason is parang is stuck trading
through their platform
forex hindi saito you probably know how
to make money
better or faster easier way than through
another middleman
okay say investment tagametron
[Music]
and ire recommended actually that's
sobering business my important thing
i like iceborn hindi now to pay
attention to insurance for some time
shout out to michael cruz
three times no critical illness
30 years ago getting diagnosed with a
major critical illness
was pretty much a death sentence but now
medical advancements have made it
possible for critical illness survivors
to enjoy
longer and more productive lives the
catch
living longer potentially exposes us to
more than one major critical illness in
our lifetime
and treatment will still cost you an arm
and a leg the second
or third time if you get coverage at all
introducing fwd's set for health plan
it's a one-of-a-kind plan that lets you
live a worry-free life
through good times and when things are
not going so well
with set for health get covered for 42
major critical illnesses and claim for
up to three times for three unrelated
major critical illnesses
up to age 75 with 100 percent coverage
each time to help you fight and recover
that's triple protection for triple
piece of mind
impressed we haven't even scratched the
surface yet
if you get diagnosed with your first
major critical illness
we'll waive all future premiums and
coverage continues
free of further charges so you can focus
on what matters most
getting well for 15 minor critical
illnesses you'll get ample coverage too
one claim up to 20 of the coverage
amount to be exact
more than enough to help you with
smaller medical expenses
which can still be a financial burden
but
what if the illnesses don't come
knocking what if life stays awesome
until you're 75
and you don't claim for a major critical
illness simple
we'll give you 100 of your premium back
no questions asked lastly what if the
unthinkable happens before you reach 75
and you pass away fwd will look
after your family by giving them 100
of your plans coverage amount so they
can financially be
worry free purchase your set for health
plan
today we've got you covered for a
lifetime
of possibilities get ready to live
on the french
[Music]
if you want to reach out to her i'll
leave her number her facebook page and
her email on the description below
also here pointing whatsapp viber
texting pointing
zoom blue jeans what did hindi face to
face
description proposal
big sign be ready to take on life's
challenges
actually stand out the statement
life is full of adventurers don't let
anything
stop me stop me big statement
celebrate life
[Music]
this page is pretty useless to be honest
it primed me to be positive in the pages
each of your illness claims must belong
to a different major critical illness
group see
groupings on next page diagnosis of
subsequent
critical illness should be at least one
year from the date of the diagnosis
of the preceding critical illness
proceeding
[Music]
you will be able to claim for a second
benefit under the cancer group
for as long as you have been declared
cancer-free at least
five years prior to the diagnosis of the
second cancer so
anka cersei malikan and usually manga
before 75 merohan cancer
chamatum roughly and today's prices are
no subsequent major critical illness
benefit will be paid
if you have already received already
a benefit due to terminal illness or
loss of independent existence
uh filipino monetary so terminal illness
okay
loss of independent existence one
selling point sa canela is
healthy life benefit which means pagindi
cannot claim anything
at age 75 okay so 75 on coverage
not 100. critical illness coverage is
until 75
and life up to 75.
i like this presentation modely absorb
great indie explains
great works of presentation it though
business reviews plus points
[Applause]
[Music]
i really don't like statements like this
we will review
and adjust the premium yum babe remo
accordingly
but with prior approval from the
insurance commission
which means
fwd shall notify you before any such
adjustments
under an insurance commission
insurance proposal in reality
time frame and to keep your word i
suppose over in a tabular explanation
presentations
yes
the use of color here is questionable
have you seen yellow and white
20 320 adult condition or from juvenile
condition
indigo podium a claim kapaka suicide
illegal or unlawful acts
for example
hiv except blood transfer
or donation
pre-existing conditions
you can claim up to three times worth of
the policy value
plus twenty percent for any minor claim
i loved the presentation very simplified
very colorful fun
so that's what i thought of the proposal
what do you guys think
this is can also request for your
personal code
from b links in the description below
already
fwd may link the description you will
just order online
thanks for watching happy
proposal
you